[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
-Thank you for the meal.
-Thank you.
[eatery owner] Thank you, bye.
[shop bell chimes, door opens]
[door closes, shop bell chimes]
EPISODE 7
Ah! [chuckles softly]
It's been a while.
It has.
I missed your gukbap.
By the way, I don't see your wife.
She passed last year.
[♪ gentle, melancholy music playing]
She said she just wanted to know
whether our son was alive or not.
I wonder if she knows now.
[exhales softly]
Even now, sometimes,
Heejun appears in my dreams.
He's probably dead.
Please find him.
So I can at least hold a funeral.
[sighs softly]
[Changun] Joo Hyera.
[♪ music fades]
[sighs softly]
Got a lot on your mind?
Are you still after Yu Seongwon?
YU SEONGWON RETURNS AFTER 4 YEARS
TO HOLD A SOLO EXHIBITION
That's why you came back here, isn't it?
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
I know how you feel.
There's always that one case
we can't forget.
But
we checked Yu Seongwon's alibi.
It's become an obsession for you.
Huh?
That's what ruins detectives.
It's not an obsession.
Yu Seongwon
will kill again.
I'm going to stop him.
[♪ music fades]
[♪ ominous music playing]
DISSOLUTION
THE SILENCE OF WHISPERING REEDS
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
[Isoo] Seongwon.
[♪ music stops]
[Seongwon] Isoo!
-Oh!
-[chuckles]
[grunts] I really missed you.
[Isoo] Me too.
Hey, this is for you.
I've never given flowers to a guy before.
[Seongwon chuckles]
Whoa, you're looking
even better than before.
It's nothing new.
Hey, you're finally starting to look
like a professional artist now.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-[chuckles]
-[sighs]
Just look at all this.
Isoo, come this way.
-You need to see this piece first.
-What?
[♪ tense suspenseful music playing]
[♪ music fades]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
All right.
Look closely. Nothing here, right?
No, nothing there.
Put your hand in and feel it.
-There's really nothing here.
-Nothing there.
And if I mix in a bit of magic
from Kyungjin's nose...
[exclaims, whispers] Now, let's see.
[grunts] Oh my gosh.
Ta-da.
Ooh, how did you do that?
There's a secret compartment.
I expected a rabbit at the very least.
[scoffs] Hey, see if there's
a secret compartment.
As if.
All right, in here,
add a bit of magic from Jin Isoo's nose,
-and voilà.
-Whoa!
So anyone can do this.
[scoffs softly]
How did you know?
It's obvious.
It's not like you have a magic pocket.
You're such a killjoy.
You told me to try.
Bro.
Park Jaeha's magic show.
These tickets are impossible to get.
You said you wanted to see it.
Those are VIP seats.
What is it?
[♪ jaunty music playing]
Magic is basically deception, isn't it?
[scoffs]
Deception?
Magic is an art.
An elevated art form
where science meets performance.
I'm not interested.
Really? I have a ticket for Dr. Yoon, too.
Really? Then I'll go. Thanks.
-You bring your girlfriend, too.
-Thanks, bro.
You can throw it away or use it
as scrap paper if you don't need it.
I'm coming, too.
Really?
If you really want it, be my guest.
[♪ music fades]
[♪ upbeat, jaunty music playing]
Oh, Detective Jin.
Hey...
Thanks for the ticket.
I really wanted to see this.
Ah, I knew you were
a cultured person, Dr. Yoon.
-What about me?
-You're just a person.
[chuckles softly]
[Dr. Yoon] Detective Joo.
You look great today.
Ah. [chuckles] Not at all.
You look great, too.
[chuckles softly]
You look awful.
Yeah, you too.
Why is he so late?
[sighs] I've never met
Kyungjin's girlfriend before.
Me neither.
Don't tease him
when his girlfriend arrives.
When do we ever tease? We congratulate.
[chuckles]
[Kyungjin] Bro!
Why are you alone?
Where's your girlfriend?
She has to work late today.
-Out of the blue?
-Yeah.
She wanted to come,
but she's been busy lately.
Too bad, then.
Shall we head inside?
[Isoo] You don't have a girlfriend,
do you?
[Kyungjin] I do.
-[Isoo] I don't think you do.
-[Kyungjin] I really do.
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ upbeat, intriguing music playing]
[♪ music slows]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[audience cheering, applauding]
[announcer] And now,
Park Jaeha's Magic Fire begins!
[audience continues cheering, applauding]
Ooh!
[♪ music slows]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[flames whooshing]
[audience gasps]
[audience exclaims in amazement]
[Isoo] Whoa!
[softly] How did he light it on fire?
[whispering] Hey, have some manners.
[clicks tongue]
I want to know what the trick is.
It's not a trick. It's art.
What's the matter with you?
[successive electrical thuds echoing]
[♪ gentle piano music playing]
There is someone I love.
She lived an unhappy life,
because her father was a violent man.
[sighs wearily]
[♪ dramatic sting]
I wanted
to make her smile.
[♪ enchanting music playing]
-[audience exclaims in awe]
-Oh...
What on earth?
-Whoa!
-Whoa.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[gasps softly]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ upbeat, lively
orchestral music playing]
[audience exclaims in amazement]
[audience applauding]
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ gentle piano music playing]
-[audience exclaims in awe]
-[Isoo] Whoa.
[♪ enchanting music playing]
[audience exclaims in awe]
Where is he going?
[♪ music fades]
[gunshot]
-Oh!
-[audience gasps]
[♪ gentle piano music playing]
[breath trembling]
[flames whoosh]
[audience gasps in shock]
-[scattered screams]
-[♪ music fades]
Whoa...
Oh!
[Junyoung] Wow.
[fire roaring]
[breathes shakily]
-[flames whoosh, roar intensely]
-[audience gasps in horror]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
-[burning wood crashes]
-[partner screams]
[screaming in horror]
Help!
[audience exclaiming in horror]
-Get everyone to safety first.
-Okay.
Help! Oh my god!
[Isoo] Everyone, it's all right.
Remain calm and follow our instructions.
[Junyoung] Everyone, please slow down.
Please evacuate in an orderly manner.
-[clamoring]
-Please walk slowly.
Please evacuate in an orderly manner.
[♪ music fades]
[Changun, over phone]
So you're saying that magician is dead?
Yes, he died in a fire
during the performance.
[sighs wearily]
I'll send forensics over.
Your team will take this case.
Yes, sir.
[line disconnects]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
How could something like this happen?
I know.
We're taking this case.
If you need an autopsy, let me know.
I'm going to go.
I'll leave you to it.
Let's get statements from people first.
-Got it.
-[Kyungjin] Got it.
[Isoo] Hmm...
Is he...
MAGIC PERFORMANCE PARTNER
JEONG DAHEE
[voice shaking] Is he really dead?
Yes.
[sobbing] How could he die like this?
[sniffling, sobbing]
How long have you
worked with Mr. Park Jaeha?
From a year ago.
So, earlier,
what happened to the casket?
I don't know.
[breath trembling] Originally,
it was supposed to open from the back.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
And then he's supposed to reappear.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
[audience applauding]
[♪ music fades]
[sobbing] I don't know how this happened.
[Isoo sighs softly]
[Hyera sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ tense pulsating music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
What could have happened here?
[voice shaking] I don't know.
STAGE DIRECTOR
LEE JIYUN
[sniffles]
The escape mechanism worked just fine.
He should've come down this way.
Could there have been
a problem with the casket?
I checked everything just before the show.
There was nothing wrong with it.
[♪ music swells]
[sobbing]
[♪ music fades]
[Kyungjin] Detective Joo!
The escape mechanism was working.
Then was something wrong with the casket?
The stage director said
nothing was wrong with it.
Who made the casket?
An engineer made it.
His workshop is right next door.
Mmm. We'll go meet him.
Okay. I'll check the security cameras.
[woman sobbing distantly]
What's that?
[sobbing grows louder]
[♪ jaunty music playing]
[sobbing stops]
TAROT MASTER
LUNA
[electricity crackling]
[♪ music fades]
So you do tarot readings here?
Yes.
I do readings for people
who win the giveaway.
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
PARK JAEHA'S MAGIC FIRE
Were you close with Park Jaeha?
I told him to be careful.
You mean you knew he was going to die?
Yes.
I had a dream.
Ah. [chuckles softly] A dream?
Like a prophetic dream?
Yes.
I've always had a kind of sixth sense
since I was little.
I have prophetic dreams
before something happens.
I even knew before my grandfather died.
Oh...
[Luna] But yesterday,
I saw it.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
So this morning, I told him to be careful,
and he said...
He said?
I have to treat it
like my last performance
and do my best.
Jaeha.
Thanks, Luna.
[♪ music fades]
Did you see anything else in that dream?
No.
Oh...
All right, thank you for your cooperation.
Wow, that's incredible.
She had a prophetic dream.
[exhales softly in awe]
You don't believe that stuff, do you?
Of course not.
[sighs]
When I was learning at the police academy,
a certain instructor said,
"Accept new information without bias."
You must've forgotten.
When you're investigating a case,
psychics call all the time,
claiming they know something.
But when you ask who did it,
they suddenly can't see it.
[scoffs softly]
More importantly,
what Park Jaeha said is bothering me.
What do you mean?
He said he had to treat it
like his last performance.
As if he knew he would die.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
I have to treat it
like my last performance
and do my best.
Let's go to the workshop.
Okay.
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ music fades]
I assume you haven't found much.
Well, everything burned to a crisp.
We'll check right away and let you know.
-Okay.
-Good luck.
-[Junyoung] Okay.
-[Kyungjin] Thank you, sir.
[Junyoung sighs]
What happened here?
And you are?
I'm the CEO of the production company.
SHOW PRODUCER
CHOI MIHEE
Did Jaeha die?
Yes, he is deceased.
How?
It seems there was a problem
with the magic equipment.
That's impossible. [scoffs in disbelief]
[Isoo] Hello?
[door unlocks]
[low, mechanical whirring]
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
Mr. Park Jaeha?
MAGIC SHOW ENGINEER
PARK JAEHYUNG
I'm Park Jaehyung.
Jaeha's brother.
You're twins.
[Isoo exhales softly]
We're with the police.
[breath trembles]
Did you hear the news?
Yes.
I heard it just now.
Is it true?
Yes.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
[chokes, sobs]
[sobbing softly]
[♪ music fades]
We heard you build the equipment yourself.
We used to perform together in the past,
but after I injured my legs,
I became an engineer.
The performance you did together
must have been a teleportation act.
That's right.
Teleportation?
We went to see a show,
and the CEO scouted us.
Because we're twins.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[chain clinking, rattling]
[♪ music swells]
[audience gasps]
[announcer] Park Jaeha's Teleportation!
[audience cheering, applauding]
-[♪ music fades]
-[Isoo] That was
done by twins?
Yes.
Jaeha was talented.
[♪ soft, melancholy music playing]
So he made his professional debut,
and I only joined him
for the teleportation act.
What exactly happened?
The casket caught on fire...
[breath trembles]
...and your brother wasn't able to escape.
[chokes back a sob]
[crying softly]
[voice shaking] I kept telling him
it was dangerous.
Are you saying the casket was dangerous?
If the fuel leaked,
it could cause an accident,
so I told him not to do it.
Then why did he...
Jaeha always said the same thing.
Don't you know how lucky I am, Jaehyung?
Things like that don't happen to me.
Okay.
It was the same
when the accident happened.
Jaeha was fine,
while I ended up like this.
So I, too,
believed that luck was on his side,
STYLE
::cue()
but then this happened. [sobbing]
[sniffles, continues sobbing]
[♪ music fades]
There's no way there was
a problem with the equipment.
Do you know how much
we rehearse before the show?
We run it dozens, even hundreds of times
without a problem
before it goes on stage.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[siren wailing]
[♪ music fades]
The production company's CEO
insists there wasn't a problem.
She wouldn't want to admit
that it was an accident.
The engineer said it was dangerous.
Hey, the engineer is the magician's twin.
-His twin?
-[Isoo] Yeah.
[sighs heavily]
To think the teleportation magic
was a trick with twins.
Obviously. Did you think
he was actually teleporting?
Do superpowers really not exist?
Let's go back for now.
We'll know once
the forensic results are out.
-Okay.
-Have a good evening.
Mr. Innocent.
[chuckles softly] Let's go.
So, which do you think it is?
I can't say for sure yet. [sighs]
But there is something strange.
Like what?
If this was indeed a murder,
why was he killed on stage?
Why create countless witnesses
by killing him during a performance?
If a magician dies during a performance,
it can be made to look like an accident.
But once it's revealed to be a murder,
that narrows down the suspects.
Only a limited number of people
have access to the equipment.
Hmm. That's true.
[cell phone ringing over car audio]
Sorry, one second.
YU SEONGWON
INCOMING CALL
Hey, Sculptor Yu.
Did the exhibition wrap up okay?
Yeah, it just finished,
so we're packing up now.
[Isoo] Hey, did you sell all your pieces?
I wanted to buy one.
I don't sell my pieces.
I keep them all.
[Isoo] Oh. Well, look at you, Mr. Artist.
I guess you don't need the money.
Isoo.
Let's meet up soon.
It's been a while since I was last here.
Yeah, we should. How long are you staying?
I have another exhibition coming up,
so I'll probably be in Korea for a while.
Got it. Then let's meet up next week.
I'll call you.
Okay, bye.
[line disconnects]
That reminds me,
you were at the exhibition.
Just look at all this.
Isoo, come this way.
You need to see this piece first.
What? Which one?
Yes, I was there.
Do you like Yu Seongwon?
I'm very interested in him.
No wonder. You had
photos of his exhibition at home.
I'm close with Seongwon.
How do you know him?
Uh...
You know his family owns UBS Group, right?
I met him at a gathering
for third-generation chaebol heirs.
I haven't seen him much
since he moved to the UK,
but he's completely fallen for my charms.
He likes me so much.
[Isoo exclaims smugly]
If you want to meet him,
I can arrange something.
Next time.
Are you feeling shy?
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
SEWON HOSPITAL
[medical monitor beeping steadily]
[♪ soft, melancholy music playing]
[Dr. Jinkyung] Mr. Choi Jeonghun,
we will now begin the surgery.
All right.
Don't worry. It's going to go well.
Just get some sleep,
and you'll wake up healthier.
Okay.
We're going to put you under now.
[anesthesiologist] We'll begin
the anesthesia now.
[Dr. Jinkyung] Please count slowly
from one to ten.
[Mr. Choi, muffled] One.
Two.
Three.
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
[Taegyun] "The magician
who burned on stage"?
Good grief.
Why did we end up
with another bothersome case?
Well...
Team 1 happened to be on site at the time.
"Happened to be"?
Well... [chuckles nervously]
Detective Jin had tickets,
so they went to see the show.
For heaven's sake.
What's wrong with him?
Is he a crime magnet? Jesus Christ.
Everywhere he goes, it's a new case.
[knock at door]
[Taegyun] Come in.
Right, yes. Put that in the car.
[sighs in exasperation]
In any case, catch the culprit quickly.
-Got it?
-Yes, sir.
-[Taegyun] Right.
PARK JAEHA, AGE 32
RENOWNED MAGICIAN
FOUND DEAD IN A FIRE DURING A PERFORMANCE
ACCIDENT? OR EQUIPMENT ERROR?
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
FIRE BREAKS OUT DURING A FIRE ESCAPE ACT
[inhales sharply]
This isn't an accident.
It's a murder case.
Kerosene was detected on the casket panel.
They normally use a special kind of oil,
but someone poured kerosene in it,
so the flames spread inside.
TRACES OF KEROSENE DETECTED
Oh, and this is
the forensic analysis of his phone.
[Junyoung scoffs softly]
[sighs] Park Jaeha was something else.
[scoffs] What's wrong this guy?
Look at this.
Let's go. They're holding
a memorial for him today.
Okay.
Come on.
Let's go.
IN MEMORY OF PARK JAEHA,
WHO GAVE US SO MANY MAGICAL MOMENTS
THE FLAMES YOU LEFT BEHIND
STILL LIVE ON IN ALL OF US
WE WILL FOREVER REMEMBER THE SMILE
THAT MADE US BELIEVE IN MAGIC
THE LATE PARK JAEHA (1992-2025)
[♪ somber, melancholy music playing]
[camera shutters clicking]
Let us have a moment of silence.
WE WON'T FORGET THE MIRACLES YOU CREATED
MAY YOU REST IN PEACE, JAEHA
Thank you.
[sniffles]
[sighs softly]
[♪ music fades]
The fans wanted to pay their respects,
so we arranged this memorial.
When can we hold the funeral?
I think this is going to take some time.
We believe someone murdered Mr. Park.
Do you know anyone
who might want him dead?
[Mihee] No, not at all.
Jaeha was always so cheerful and kind.
He wasn't the kind of person
anyone would hate.
[sobbing] How could something
like this happen?
This is just so horrible.
[continues sobbing]
The truth is,
I was in a relationship with him.
[♪ jaunty music playing]
What are you talking about?
It's been 50 days.
[scoffs]
I've dated him for over a year.
I'm sure you just had a crush.
You dated him?
Are you sure you didn't imagine it?
Jaeha bought this for me.
STYLE
::cue()
-[scoffs] Me too.
-Me too.
[Jiyun] He bought it for you?
No way.
I'm sure it was as a thank-you.
You're the one who's delusional.
Jaeha has really high standards.
Yeah, you're way older than him, too.
What does age have to do with anything?
He called you immature and tacky.
[scoffs]
You mean "pure and innocent."
He said he discovered true love
only after meeting me.
[scoffs] We kept it a secret,
but we were going to get married
next year.
We were looking
for a place to move in together
-and register our marriage next month.
-Marriage?
[sighs deeply]
There's no way.
Why would he be into you two?
What? Watch what you say.
You watch what you say.
Don't say whatever you want
just because he's dead!
-Hey!
-[Dahee] Move in together? As if.
I'm the one Jaeha truly loved.
It's neither of you.
I'm the one he chose in the end.
He told me you stalked him.
How dare you! Come here.
[Isoo] Wait, hold on. Break it up.
Violence is wrong.
[Dahee] What do you want?
We're in the middle
of something important.
I know. It sounds pretty serious.
But that something important is
pointless now.
I checked Mr. Park Jaeha's phone records.
Uh...
-Jiyun?
-Yes.
-You're "Honey 1."
-What?
-And Dahee.
-Yes?
-You're "Honey 2."
-What?
-Luna?
-Yes?
You're "Honey 6."
Six?
What's that supposed to mean?
It means
Mr. Park Jaeha had a lot of girlfriends.
In other words, you were all his honeys.
There were seven honeys in total.
[whispering] He must have
so much love to give.
[stuttering] Seven people?
Didn't you always go on dates
on the same day each week?
Seven women, seven days.
It must be Monday, Tuesday, and Saturday.
Hold on.
These are all fakes.
You lent him money too, right?
-[gasps]
-Let's talk at the station.
-Detective Park.
-Yes.
-[Isoo] Let's go.
-[sighs]
-[Junyoung] Come on.
-Just for some small talk.
It's part of the investigation.
Come on, honeys.
Let's talk at the station.
[♪ music fades]
Murder?
You mean...
someone killed Jaeha?
Yes.
Someone poured kerosene inside the casket.
Who?
Do you know if there was anyone
who wanted to kill your brother?
If anyone comes to mind, please tell us.
No.
Jaeha was the type of person
who was always in the spotlight.
[♪ gentle piano music playing]
[applauding]
Everyone loved him.
A little too much, I think.
Sorry?
We've confirmed
that Mr. Park had seven girlfriends.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
He was always popular.
It wasn't that he was popular.
He was a womanizer.
He dated seven women at once.
Was he in trouble at all
because of a woman?
Did he say anything of the sort?
No.
[sighs softly]
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
[Dahee] He said it'd be awkward
if other people found out,
and that we should keep it a secret.
Workplace relationships are never easy.
[clears throat]
Did you really not know he was cheating?
Uh...
I did notice something that felt off.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[both chuckle softly]
You're upset with me, aren't you?
It's just weird.
We're just good friends
because we've worked together for so long.
I have this beautiful,
adorable girlfriend,
so why would I look at anyone else?
[scoffs incredulously]
Wait.
You're blinding me.
[scoffs]
When I look into your eyes,
I see diamonds.
[squeals]
And it's right here.
Oh my god!
When did you prepare this?
It's nothing much.
[softly] Ah...
[Jaeha chuckles softly]
-[keyboard clacking]
-[♪ music fades]
[Junyoung] "When I look into your eyes,
I see diamonds."
So that's the kind of thing
women like to hear.
He was really affectionate.
[♪ gentle piano music playing]
Your pretty hands are all beat up.
It's fine.
-Want me to show you my new magic trick?
-Yes.
It's a ring.
It's beautiful.
[Jiyun gasps]
Oh my god.
That's amazing.
[gasps softly]
Where did it go?
[chuckles softly]
Will you marry me?
[whimpers softly]
-[patron 1] Congratulations.
-[patron 2] Way to go.
[patron 3] Congratulations.
[patrons cheering, applauding]
[♪ soft, melancholy music playing]
JAEHA "WILL YOU MARRY ME?"
Getting down on your knees
and proposing in a public place
is something women hate, isn't it?
It depends on the person.
[whispering] He's new to dating.
But I was still number one,
so he must have liked me best, right?
-You were just the longest.
-[keyboard clacking]
[♪ jaunty music playing]
[sighs in exasperation]
I thought it was destiny.
Pick a card.
[both gasp softly]
Once more.
[Jaeha hums drumroll, chuckles]
[both] Oh!
-What on earth?
-One last time.
[Jaeha] Oh!
How did you do it?
STYLE
::cue()
[Jaeha chuckles]
I didn't do anything.
I told you, it's destiny.
Oh, you.
Why did he say he needed to borrow money?
He said he needed it for his brother.
For a car accident.
To get a place to live.
He said he'd pay it back quickly.
-[exhales deeply]
-[sighs thoughtfully]
[♪ music fades]
How much did you lend him?
-Two hundred thousand?
-Two million won.
-Are you crazy?
-[sighs softly]
I even cashed out my savings.
DETECTIVE DIVISION
[♪ jaunty, dramatic music playing]
NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
Let's go have some soju.
And think about
how to exhume and desecrate him.
What does that mean?
It means taking him out of the grave
and killing him again.
[♪ music fades]
Even so,
would they have killed him for cheating?
He was cheating on seven people.
Any one of them
could've been angry enough.
Oh.
They won't have known.
Jaeha can be quite meticulous.
Then who could it be?
[♪ suspenseful, melancholy music playing]
[voice shaking] I honestly...
have no idea.
I know him best.
He's not the type of person
anyone would hate.
Who in the world...
could have done such a horrible thing?
I really,
honestly don't know.
[sobs]
[sighs heavily]
[thud]
-[gasps]
-[dove cooing]
[♪ upbeat, jaunty music playing]
-[air hisses]
-[gasps, yelps]
[in English] Magic show.
[in Korean] You shouldn't touch anything.
There's a lot of interesting things here.
[♪ music fades]
He's the killer.
What? Where did that come from?
He was about to get up just now.
I didn't see it.
You're not very observant for a detective.
I was too busy being embarrassed
by your dove flying act.
I saw it with my own two eyes.
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
Maybe his legs have healed.
He hid that fact and killed his brother.
-Why?
-His motive was
jealousy.
They're twins,
but Jaeha lived the high life,
doing magic and cheating on women.
Whereas he's stuck in a wheelchair.
[sighs deeply]
STYLE
::cue()
LOVER'S REVENGE?
PARK JAEHA, HONEY 1 LEE JIYUN
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
HONEY 2 JEONG DAHEE, HONEY 6 LUNA
STAGE DIRECTOR,
PERFORMANCE PARTNER, TAROT MASTER
I don't think the three of them
knew he was cheating.
-You sure they're not acting?
-Didn't seem like it.
-Did you check on the kerosene?
-[Kyungjin] Yes.
I called all the gas stations
near the theater,
but no one's bought kerosene recently.
PARK JAEHYUNG
What about his brother?
He says there isn't anyone
who'd want to kill him.
INVOLVED WITH MULTIPLE WOMEN
SIGNS OF FINANCIAL EXPLOITATION
He also didn't know he was a cheater.
[sighs wearily] I really think
the brother is suspicious.
-[♪ music fades]
-What do you mean?
I made a dove fly out earlier.
-A dove?
-Why?
While stumbling around.
It's an investigative technique. Look.
I made the dove... You do it.
I made the dove fly out like this,
then Mr. Park Jaehyung
suddenly flinched like this.
[scoffs]
[Kyungjin] Then, you mean
he's able to walk?
Exactly.
No way.
I think he's able to walk, but pretended
not to and killed his brother.
[sighs] Do you agree with him,
Detective Joo?
I don't know.
Let's check the outside security footage.
Okay.
[♪ tense, ticking music playing]
[inhales deeply, exhales]
[mouse clicking]
Ms. Lee Jiyun said
nothing was wrong with the casket, right?
Yes, she last checked around 4:30 p.m.
Oh, there's the casket.
[in English] Okay.
[in Korean] She checked the casket
at 4:30 p.m.
The show started at 5:00 p.m.
The fire broke out at 5:50 p.m.
If Mr. Park Jaehyung messed with
the equipment after Ms. Lee checked it,
he would've left the workshop
between 4:30 and 5:50 p.m.
I heard they return the equipment
to the workshop after the show.
Ah, when we went,
Mr. Park Jaehyung was inside the workshop.
He never left.
That's the only way out
for someone in a wheelchair.
My gut tells me it's him.
If, just like I said,
he could walk, he can crawl
out of the window and go around.
And avoid the cameras.
You're obsessing again.
My gut's telling me.
-Let's investigate the brother too.
-See? She trusts my instincts.
It's just to check.
Then I'll look into him tomorrow.
[Hyera] Okay.
Hey.
[♪ tense pulsating music playing]
Could Ms. Lee Jiyun
and Mr. Park Jaehyung be accomplices?
A betrayed woman
and a jealous brother working together.
[♪ music fades]
-I'm going home.
-Me too.
Hey, I'm not done explaining my theory.
[Hyera] You should go home, too.
[♪ jaunty music plays]
SEWON HOSPITAL
[knock on door]
-[gasps] Ah.
-[door closes]
How are you feeling?
I'm doing better than I thought.
That's always the case.
Thinking about it is the scariest part.
Once it's over,
you realize it's not so bad after all.
That happens quite often.
[chuckles] You're right.
I heard you're the chairman of a company,
STYLE
::cue()
but it's been so quiet.
Uh...
I didn't want to bother my staff,
so I didn't tell them.
I just took time off work.
What about your wife?
I'm not married.
I never got the chance.
That's wise of you.
I've been there.
[sighs regretfully]
-[chuckling]
-Ah. [chuckles softly]
But you must feel lonely
being by yourself at night.
Well,
it's nice and quiet. [chuckles]
I understand.
Get plenty of sleep.
That's the best medicine.
[chuckles]
Call for us if you're in pain.
I will. [chuckles]
-Go on home.
-All right.
Bye.
[door opens]
-[door closes]
-[exhales in relief]
It's 11:00 p.m. on October 12, 2023,
at Jangseon-dong.
October 12.
JANGSEON-DONG DUI COLLISION
INVESTIGATION REPORT
-Seongjun.
-Yes?
You responded to this accident, right?
The one with the twins.
-[Seongjun] Yes, I did.
-What happened?
A vehicle crashed into a building.
The driver was heavily intoxicated.
Who was the driver?
It was the younger of the twins.
Mr. Park Jaeha.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
It's funny how luck works.
The drunk driver wasn't even wearing
a seatbelt, but he was completely fine,
whereas his brother was badly hurt.
[♪ music swells, fades]
Mr. Park Jaehyung has
a traumatic spinal cord injury,
so he is unable to walk.
Is there any chance,
even the slightest chance,
that he could miraculously stand up
and walk again?
Not even a tiny chance?
If a miracle happened, he could walk.
That's what a miracle is, isn't it?
Right. That's true.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
[sighs wearily]
That looks suspicious.
[Hyera] It does.
-Check who owns the vehicle.
-Okay.
[keyboard clacking]
VEHICLE REGISTRATION SEARCH
[♪ music increases in tempo]
OWNER HAM SEONGWOOK
Ham Seongwook.
He did have a motive.
Park Jaeha crashed the car
while driving drunk,
and his brother was injured.
[Isoo clicks tongue, inhales deeply]
That accident left him paralyzed
from the waist down.
Is there a chance he could walk?
Yes.
-If a miracle happened.
-[♪ music fades]
Oh, come on.
Anyway, come look at this.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[keyboard key clacks]
[Hyera] This is three days
before the incident.
[keyboard key clacks]
The vehicle is owned by Ham Seongwook.
Ham Seongwook?
You mean that Ham Seongwook?
Yes.
I thought he retired.
I thought so too, but maybe not.
Who's Ham Seongwook?
He's the boss of Hammurabi,
the biggest crime syndicate in Seoul.
[victim whimpers, mutters]
[yelping in terror]
[breathing frantically]
FORMER BOSS OF HAMMURABI CLAN
HAM SEONGWOOK
[♪ music increases in tempo]
-[blunt thud]
-[victim exclaims]
[♪ music fades]
He got 12 years for soliciting murder,
and he's been quiet since he got out.
What would a gangster want
with a magician?
We'll have to find out.
Oh!
There were some guys who looked like
thugs sitting behind us at the theater.
[♪ tense pulsating music playing]
[whispering] Please stop
kicking my seat, okay?
[softly] Are your legs too long?
Yeah, you're right.
They were there
on the day of the incident.
[keyboard clacks]
[keyboard key clacks]
Let's find out where Ham Seongwook is
and also identify those thugs.
-Got it.
-[Kyungjin] Got it.
-Do you remember their faces?
-Of course.
They had terrible manners.
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
[Isoo sighs] Look at these faces.
They look mean as hell.
You really can tell a lot from a face.
Any idea who they are?
Mmm-mmm. Not in the slightest.
Look at them.
They all look the same. [sighs softly]
Detective Joo!
I found out how Ham Seongwook
and Park Jaeha know each other.
[♪ suspenseful, ticking music playing]
Here.
[Isoo] Ham Sujeong?
That name sounds familiar.
Ham Sujeong is...
[in English] "...Honey 7."
[in Korean] She's his only daughter,
born when he was 40.
[in English] Honey 7.
HONEY 7 HAM SUJEONG
[in Korean] We couldn't reach her.
Yes, she left for LA a week ago
and won't answer her phone.
His only daughter fell for a womanizer.
Of course he'd want to kill him.
Did he send his daughter to the US
and kill him while she was gone?
[taps table] I just got goosebumps.
His show was about Ham Sujeong.
There is someone I love.
She lived an unhappy life,
because her father
was a violent man.
[gasps] You're right. The violent father!
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
He saw the performance three days prior
and planned to use
the casket in his murder?
He snuck backstage
and poured kerosene inside the casket.
Would that be possible?
I think it's possible.
But why didn't he just kill Park Jaeha
when he took him three days ago?
He was making a statement.
"Are you saying my daughter is
unhappy because of me?"
"Then I'll kill you for real on stage."
[♪ music swells, fades]
I can't get a location on Ham Seongwook.
And he won't answer his phone.
Did you find out his address?
Yes.
IDENTITY RECORD
HAM SEONGWOOK
Let's go and see what happens.
Detective Choi,
send Dr. Yoon the autopsy request.
Got it.
Jin Isoo, come with me.
[♪ suspenseful, ticking music playing]
[engine purrs, brakes squeal]
[♪ rock music sting plays, fades]
[doorbell chiming]
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
[Isoo] The lights are on.
[line connects, ringing]
STYLE
::cue()
[vehicle approaching]
[car door closes]
Can I help you?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
It's him. The guy who kicked my seat.
-[exclaiming]
-Let go.
[exclaims in pain]
[groans]
What do you want?
We're with the police.
-Him, too?
-[scoffs]
Uh...
Yes, police.
No need to make a fuss. Go inside.
[henchman] Yes, sir.
-Get moving.
-Get back inside.
What's your name?
DIRECTOR BAEK CHULMIN
Mr. Baek Chulmin.
You were there
on the day Mr. Park Jaeha died.
It was a spectacular show.
He burned pretty well.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Did you kill him?
[chuckles]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
You're barking up the wrong tree.
If I'd killed him,
you would never have found the body.
Hey...
He's lying.
His eyes shifted.
They're shifting.
[♪ music swells, stops]
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
Did you meet Mr. Park
three days before the incident?
-We had a chat.
-About what?
That bastard messed
with our boss's daughter.
So we just had a word with him.
Isn't it the Hammurabi way
to pay back in kind?
[scoffs] You've gone soft.
We need to meet Mr. Ham Seongwook.
-He's inside, right?
-The chairman
doesn't speak to cops.
[scoffs]
Everyone and their dog
is a chairman these days.
A chairman of what?
Of a makgeolli club? Huh?
What? Think I'm scared?
Let's end it here.
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
[sighs in exasperation]
Move your car,
and teach your kid how to behave.
-Kid? You're calling me a kid?
-[♪ music fades]
-[scoffs]
-[gate closes]
He's proud of being a thug, is that it?
Acting all tough. [clicks tongue]
I think we need to meet Ham Seongwook.
Call him in.
[sighs]
Like he'd come.
[Isoo groans]
STYLE
::cue()
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
FATHER AND DAUGHTER
HONEY 7 HAM SUJEONG, HAM SEONGWOOK
You're all working hard.
Here's the file on Ham Seongwook.
Go pay him a visit.
Okay, thank you.
-Thank you, sir!
[door opens]
[door closes]
Do we really have to go this far
just to meet a mob boss?
If he's refusing to cooperate,
he's hiding something.
We need to meet him fast.
MOVEMENT REPORT
HERITAGE SHOOTING CLUB
WEEKLY VISIT EVERY WEDNESDAY
Tomorrow's Wednesday.
[♪ upbeat, jaunty music playing]
I'll arrange a meeting.
Jin Isoo, what's going on?
Just sit back and relax for now.
I'll let you know.
What's with him?
He's thought of a way.
We just need to wait.
[♪ music fades]
DETECTIVE JIN ISOO
[cell phone vibrating]
[groans softly]
[grunts]
[cell phone continues vibrating]
[exhales softly]
Detective Jin.
[Isoo] Mr. Choi, are you busy?
No, I'm not.
What is it?
I have a favor to ask.
All right.
I'll get it taken care of right away.
Thank you. You're the best.
[chuckles softly]
Mr. Choi.
Yes?
Why do you sound so down?
I don't sound down at all.
You're not unwell, are you?
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
Okay, I'll leave that with you.
[sighs softly]
-[line disconnects]
-[sighs weekly]
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
HERITAGE SHOOTING CLUB
I'm sorry, but we are
unable to accommodate you today.
What do you mean?
He comes here every Wednesday.
I'm really sorry.
The truth is, the owner told us
not to let anyone in today.
The owner? You mean Mr. Park?
[club manager] Well,
the owner has changed as of today.
STYLE
::cue()
The guy's got no manners.
-Who is it?
-[Isoo] It's me.
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
[exhales smugly]
We finally get to meet.
Mr. Gangster, Ham Seongwook.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
[gunshot]
[microphone feedback]
[♪ upbeat pop music playing,
Hersh "Shadows In The Night"]
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 7
A FACE-OFF WITH HAM SEONGWOOK!
Special Cast.
Son Woohyeon, Heo Sungtae, Jung Chaeyeon
-I won't ever see her again!
-Cut him.
[Sujeong] Dad.
Did you kill him?
Let's go back to the beginning.
[Kyungjin] I know who bought the kerosene.
[Hyera] That's Ms. Lee Jiyun.
[Junyoung] There was a kerosene heater
in the workshop.
[Hyera] He wanted to kill his brother
out of jealousy?
Were you in on it from the start?
-[Junyoung] Should start with this one.
-[Isoo, in English] Oh my god.
[in Korean] Pack up and leave quickly.
I can't return to the UK. [chuckles]
Two of Yu Seongwon's models disappeared.
-[bartender] Who is she?
-Someone obsessed with me.
I'm thinking of using her as a model.
[Isoo] You just need to use me.
-I'll do anything you need.
-[♪ music fades]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Seven women?
[inhales sharply, exhales]
Yes.
[scoffs]
My Sujeong...
is... [in English] "Honey 7"?
[♪ music swells]
-[in Korean] Go bring that bastard in.
-[♪ music fades]
Translated by Hyesoo Lee